/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data6_4', {
    title: '6.4 Reduce Fractions',
    path: '6.4-reduce-fractions',
    children: [{
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{2}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{6}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{15}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{5}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{15}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{15}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{24}}{\\str{28}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\input{7}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{24}}{\\fracstr{28}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{24}}{\\fracstr{28}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{3}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{13}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{13}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{13}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{13}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{14}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{2}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{14}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{14}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{6}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{10}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{10}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{21}}{\\str{35}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{5}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{21}}{\\fracstr{35}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{21}}{\\fracstr{35}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{8}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{4}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Reduce Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{48}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{4}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Reduce \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{12}}{\\fracstr{48}}}{\\str{\xA0 to its lowest terms }}',
                answer: '\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\fracstr{12}}{\\fracstr{48}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
